

# CONTACT

joelanthonybond@gmail.
com

(575) 921 1344

https://www.linkedin.co

m/in/bondcsm/

Nob Hill, ABQ, 87106

#### **EDUCATION**

# BACHELOR OF LIBERAL ARTS

2015

University of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM

## **SKILLS**

- CRMs Salesforce, Jira, Trello
- Conflict Resolution
- Customer Service
- Documentation
   Organization
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Project Management
- QA Manual Testing

#### REFERENCES

- Josephine Vasiljevic Agile Group USA Phone: (505) 944 - 5217, Email: jvasiljevic@agilegroupusa.com
- Eddy Archibeque Phone: (505) 331-2339 Email: earchibeque@salud.unm.edu
- Govinda Tamburino Software
  Developer Consultant Phone: (786)
  355 9966, Email:
  gto16108@gmail.com
- Kristin Gerhard Steiner, Marketing, Presbyterian Healthcare Services, 505.923.5288, ksteiner@phs.org

# JOEL BOND

Scrum Master / Business Analyst

#### **ABOUT**

A results-driven Certified Scrum Master and Technical Business Analyst with over 5 years of experience supporting and managing enterprise solutions for government systems, education, research, and IT organizations. Experienced with leading and providing project and people management, software testing, alongside strategic process awareness and improvements for public and private customers.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BUSINESS ANALYST**

New Mexico Department of Health | Santa Fe, NM | June 2019 - Current | Contract Hired on as a consultant to provided project management and business analysis. My

primary focus is to provide a Discovery of current asset and inventory policies in place and to provide an alternative solution better suited for enterprise asset and inventory management. (See LinkedIn for more information)

#### **SCRUM MASTER / BUSINESS ANALYST**

RHT Consultant: Presbyterian Health Services | ABQ, NM | Jan 2019 - June 2019 | Contract Developed and built knowledge across the project lifecycle including scope definition, business case development, requirements gathering, functional and technical design, vendor assessment, testing, training, and implementation phases. Responsible for the planning and facilitation of standard scrum ceremonies to include; backlog preparation, iteration planning, retrospectives, iteration reviews and daily stand-ups.

## **PROJECT MANAGER**

Advanced Network Management | Albuquerque, NM | July 2018 - Jan 2019 | Contract

A customer-focused Project Manager/Scrum Master with a passion to drive process, consistency and communication to meet customer retention and satisfaction goals within an assigned account (client) portfolio. Assumed primary responsibility for coordination and communication on all assigned projects including development and monitoring of project plans, work schedules, status reports, and other deliverables.

#### **BUSINESS ANALYST / PROJECT COORDINATOR**

Agile Group USA | Albuquerque, NM | Nov 2016 - July 2018 | Contract

Provided support and training life cycle support for USACE PROMIS (P2) Training Program and specialized in removing impediments for continuous delivery. Defined and communicated product roadmaps with the executive team and business partners. Assisted project managers and instructors in coordinating publications including training manuals, rosters, and other supporting training. DOD Cleared.